OK, hello everyone.
I'm Fish.
So this video is mainly to introduce
Nanuo Banana Two.
I ran the case all day today.
The actual effect
is still very, very amazing.
Almost every picture is very perfect.
was generated according to my prompt words
The specific effect
you can see in the demo at the beginning
This time,
I have deployed it both in the cloud and locally
As for RH,
because Mr. Wen has just lowered the price
I think it's worth playing.
Because now one thousand and two thousand is also twenty-five cents.
Four K is a little more expensive,
is fifty cents
is also my most commonly used cloud platform
When you register for the first time, you will get one thousand points.
and you'll get one hundred points every day you log in
Then for the local version,
due to the price of the Zhenzhen Gongfu, is very favorable.
and the discount period is still going on,
whether it's one K, two K, or four K, the price is zero point two.
So it’s also worth using the local version.
So after I finish the stream,
I will tell you
how to install the local API call.
So let's start with Text-to-Image.
Text-to-Image is actually very simple
We just need to write here, and we can write the prompt word we want
As for the writing of the prompt word,
we can refer to the way we use
whether it's Doubao
or other intelligent agents to describe it. Just write it.
Don't write it yourself.
Try to use the intelligent body to complete the things we want.
Single Image/Images Generates Images, as for the ratio, it is set here, which is the proportion of the drawing.
Then it supports many
Then just choose according to your needs.
There are no other differences.
Then the cloud side
I choose two K for everyone.
because four K is more expensive.
The quality of two K is actually enough for me
And here is the master switch.
For single image,
Well, it's actually with Text-to-Image.
there is no difference.
It's just a matter of accessing the image.
For single image, it's just that you need to change
what you want to change.
Or is it a way of writing a prompt word?
For dual, triple, and quadruple images,
In general,
is exactly the same as the previous gameplay
but the process is simpler
The effects are even better.
The most important thing is the prompt word
So what do you want to achieve
you still need to describe it through an agent
We will try to make a prompt word template
The prompt template will, finally I will tell you
I will put it in my cloud drive.
In my cloud drive,
I have sorted out eight types of templates.
You can also refer to it.
Then according to the style of the template.
to let the agent generate more different types of templates.
Okay.
You just need to tell it.
There's not much to say about the flow.
Because this is really the simplest usage.
Because as long as you call the API,
all the processes become very simple.
So I mainly want to tell you
how to call the local one.
Because the local price is really very good.
whether it's four K, two K, or one K, it's all zero point two.
First of all, we need to first
download this plugin.
use the advanced options of QiuYe.
Install the new extension in Version Management.
and then paste it here.
Well, this is still very simple.
Because I took a look
there is almost no conflict with the environment.
After installation,
you just need to open my stream.
and you can use it normally.
The main thing is the registration for the Zhenzhen AI workshop.
After you register for the AI Workshop,
After you finish registering your account,
you can enter the token section.
If you register for the first time,
you will get zero point two yuan.
Then you need to recharge first.
You need to recharge first
Then add the token here.
Just enter any name here
and submit it.
we just need to fill in here,
It's very simple to use.
So how to use the specific test?
You can do it according to your own ideas
As for the Netdisk, it's a workflow.
It's a prompt template as I just told you.
And the specific download address
you can check my top comment later, that's enough.
Okay, that's all for this video.
I think Nana Banana is worth playing for everyone.
Because the current price is not high.
Whether from a commercial perspective
or from a usage perspective,
it's really much better than all the models we've played before, it's much better
much much better
That's all for this video.